Guide to the Jack Anderson papers, 1930-2004 MS2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Merry-Go-Round columns, 1934-2004; 1948-2004; MS2001 Series 1; 79.5 Linear Feet 159 document boxes
  - Typescripts, Undated
    - Typescript, 1975 March (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1975 March (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1975 April (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1975 April (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1975 April (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1975 May (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Typescript, 1975 May (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1975 May (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1975 June (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1975 June (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1975 June (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript, 1975 July (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1975 July (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1975 July (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1975 August (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1975 August (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1975 August (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1975 September (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1975 September (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript, 1975 October (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1975 October (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1975 October (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1975 November (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1975 November (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1975 November (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1975 December (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1975 December (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1975 December (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 January (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 January (Box 429, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1976 January (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 January (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 February (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 February (Box 429, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1976 February (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 February (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 March (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 March (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - Typescript, 1976 March (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 March (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 April (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 April (Box 429, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1976 April (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 April (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 May (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 May (Box 429, Folder 5)
    - Typescript, 1976 May (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 May (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 June (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 June (Box 429, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1976 June (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 June (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 July (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 July (Box 429, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1976 July (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 July (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 August (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 August (Box 429, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1976 August (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 August (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 September (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 September (Box 429, Folder 9)
    - Typescript, 1976 September (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 September (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 October (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 October (Box 429, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1976 October (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 October (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 November (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 November (Box 429, Folder 11)
    - Typescript, 1976 November (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 November (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1976 December (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript [2 of 2], 1976 December (Box 429, Folder 12)
    - Typescript, 1976 December (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1976 December (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 January (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Typescript, 1977 January (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1977 January (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 February (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1977 February (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1977 February (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 March (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1977 March (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1977 March (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 April (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1977 April (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1977 April (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 May (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1977 May (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1977 May (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 June (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1977 June (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1977 June (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 July (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1977 July (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1977 July (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 August (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1977 August (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1977 August (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 September (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1977 September (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1977 September (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 October (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1977 October (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1977 October (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 November (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1977 November (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1977 November (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1977 December (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1977 December (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Typescript for indexing, 1977 December (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 January (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1978 January (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 February (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1978 February (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 March (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1978 March (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 April (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1978 April (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 May (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Typescript, 1978 May (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 June (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Typescript, 1978 June (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 July (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1978 July (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 August (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Typescript, 1978 August (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 September (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1978 September (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 October (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1978 October (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 November (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1978 November (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1978 December (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1978 December (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 January (Box 400, Folder 1)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 January (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 January (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 February (Box 400, Folder 2)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 February (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 February (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 March (Box 400, Folder 3)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 March (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 March (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 April (Box 400, Folder 4)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 April (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 April (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 May (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 May (Box 400, Folder 5)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 May (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 May (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 June (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 June (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 June (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 July (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 July (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 July (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 August (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 August (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 August (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 September (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 September (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 September (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 October (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 October (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 October (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 November (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 November (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 November (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1979 December (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1979 December (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1979 December (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 January (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 January (Box 400, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1980 January (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 January (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 February (Box 400, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1980 February (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 February (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 March (Box 400, Folder 8)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1980 March (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1980 March (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 March (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 April (Box 400, Folder 9)
    - Typescript, 1980 April (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 April (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 May (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 May (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1980 May (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 May (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 June (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1980 June (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 June (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 July (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 July (Box 401, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1980 July (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 July (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 August (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 August (Box 401, Folder 3)
    - Typescript, 1980 August (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 August (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 September (Box 401, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1980 September (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 September (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 October (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 October (Box 401, Folder 5)
    - Typescript, 1980 October (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 October (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 November (Box 401, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1980 November (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 November (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 December (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1980 December (Box 401, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1980 December (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1980 December (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 January (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1981 January (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 January (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 February (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 February (Box 401, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1981 February (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 February (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 March (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 March (Box 401, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 March (Box 401, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1981 March (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 March (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 April (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 April (Box 402, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1981 April (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 April (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 May (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1981 May (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 May (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 June (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1981 June (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 June (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 July (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1981 July (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 July (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 August (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1981 August (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 August (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 September (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1981 September (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 September (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 October (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 October (Box 402, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 October (Box 402, Folder 3)
    - Typescript, 1981 October (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 October (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 November (Box 402, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1981 November (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 November (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1981 December (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 December (Box 402, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1981 December (Box 402, Folder 6)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1981 December (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 January (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1982 January (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 January (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 February (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1982 February (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 February (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 March (Box 402, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 March (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, 1982 March (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 March (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 April (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 April (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - Typescript, 1982 April (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 April (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 May (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 May (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Typescript, 1982 May (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 May (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 June (Box 403, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 June (Box 403, Folder 7)
    - Typescript, 1982 June (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 June (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 July (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 July (Box 404, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 July (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1982 July (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 July (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 August (Box 404, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 August (Box 404, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1982 August (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 August (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 September (Box 404, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 September (Box 404, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1982 September (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 September (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 October (Box 404, Folder 7)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 October (Box 404, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1982 October (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 October (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 November (Box 405, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 November (Box 405, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1982 November (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 November (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 December (Box 405, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 1982 December (Box 405, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1982 December (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1982 December (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1983 January (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 January (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1983 February (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 February (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1983 March (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 March (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1983 April (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 April (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1983 May (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 May (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1983 June (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 June (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1983 July (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 July (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1983 August (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 August (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1983 September (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 September (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1983 October (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 October (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1983 November (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 November (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1983 December (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1983 December (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1984 January (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 January (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1984 February (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 February (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1984 March (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 March (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1984 April (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 April (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1984 May (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 May (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1984 June (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 June (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1984 July (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 July (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1984 August (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 August (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1984 September (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 September (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1984 October (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 October (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1984 November (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 November (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1984 December (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1984 December (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1985 January (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 January (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1985 February (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 February (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1985 March (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 March (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1985 April (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 April (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1985 May (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 May (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1985 June (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 June (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1985 July (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 July (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1985 August (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 August (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1985 September (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 September (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1985 October (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 October (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1985 November (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 November (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1985 December (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1985 December (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1986 January (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 January (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1986 February (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 February (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1986 March (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 March (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1986 April (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 April (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1986 May (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 May (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1986 June (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 June (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1986 July (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 July (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1986 August (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 August (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1986 September (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 September (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1986 October (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 October (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1986 November (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 November (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1986 December (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1986 December (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1987 January (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 January (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1987 February (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 February (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1987 March (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 March (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1987 April (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 April (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1987 May (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 May (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1987 June (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 June (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1987 July (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 July (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Typescript, 1987 August (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 August (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Typescript, 1987 September (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 September (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Typescript, 1987 October (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 October (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, 1987 November (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 November (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Typescript, 1987 December (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1987 December (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1988 January (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Typescript [2/2], 1988 January (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Camera-ready copy, 1988 January (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Typescript [1/2], 1988 February (Box 137, Folder 1)